<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<translation>
	<WelcomeName>
		<english>Welcome</english>
	</WelcomeName>
	
	<WelcomeDescription>
		<english><![CDATA[<style type="text/css"><!--
a:link, a:visited { text-decoration: none; color: #d5ac00; }
a:hover { text-decoration: underline; color: #d5ac00; }
hr { width:100%; color:black; background-color:black; height:1px; margin-bottom:0px; }
#footnote { font-size:10px; }
--></style>
<h3>Welcome to Your virtual Dark Eye!</h3>
<p>Using DereGlobus, you can view the world from the perspective of a god, glide over it linke a dragon, and explore it in a way normally reserved to Aves himself. Dive into space and time and see connections which you have not been aware of before. Let your gaze glide over Dere from the sixth spere and slowly come closer.</p>
<p>Already you can make out the different <em><strong>continents</strong></em>. Your gaze moves on and you see a small battered region in the east of Aventuria - White Tobria. Comming closer, several <em><strong>cities</strong></em> emerge, which provide additinal information on closer inspection. At a glance, you can capture the <em><strong>landscape</strong></em> and the <em><strong>borders</strong></em>, drawing closer to the capital - Perainefurten.</p>
<p>Gather information on where you can find taverns in this city or take a walk arround the courtyard of the Paraine monastery or other <strong><em>buildings</em></strong>. The eventful history of the country is accessible in the <em><strong>chronicles</strong></em>, taking you on a trip through time to see the invasion of the Desecrator of the Spheres. If you want to get an overview over the different <strong><em>publications</em></strong> about this region or even get detailed information about the locations in adventures - this is possible as well! </p>
<p><b>Read on (German only): <a href="http://www.dereglobus.org/dokumentation/handbuch/ueberblick">Was ist DereGlobus?</a></b></p>
<p>We whish you a lot of fun<br />
Your DereGlobus-Team</p>
<div style="text-align: center">
<img src="http://www.dereglobus.orkenspalter.de/public/DereGlobus/Menue/media/DereGlobus_Logo.png" alt="DereGlobus Beta" align="center" /></div>]]></english>
	</WelcomeDescription>
</translation>